Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music collection
  - 12 inch vinyl
    - Numbered by Bambaataa
      - 994 - Eyesight; Spank, 1978; SR-8695; Brown, James, 1933-2006. (Box 128)
        "Not for Sale Promotional copy" From Polydor album PD-1-6140 "Jam/1980's".
      - 995 - Close encounters, 1978; SR-8696; Page, Gene. (Box 128)
        Promotional only.
      - 996 - Chic., 1977; SR-8697; Chic (Musical group) (Box 128)
      - 996 - Eruption., 1978; SR-8698 (Box 128)
        Ariola American Records
      - 997 - Take me to the next phase, 1978; SR-8699; Isley Brothers. (Box 128)
        "Demonstration, Not for Sale."_x000D_ Taken from the T-Neck LP: "Showdown" JZ34930._x000D_ Special disco version of the T-Neck single: ZS8 2272.
      - 998 - Pride, 1977; SR-8700; Isley Brothers. (Box 128)
        "Demonstration, Not for Sale."_x000D_ Taken from the T-Neck LP: "Go for your guns" PZ34432._x000D_ Special disco version of the T-Neck single: ZS8 2262.
      - 998 - Pride (part 1 & 2); Hope you feel better love (part 1 & 2), 1977; SR-8701; Isley Brothers. (Box 128)
        "The pride" is special disco version from the T-Neck LP: "Go for your guns" PZ34432; "Hope you feel better love" is special disco version frm the T-Neck LP: "The heat is on" PZ33536.
      - 999 - Bombers., 1978; SR-8702; Bombers (Disco group) (Box 128)
        Quebec, Canada
      - 1000 - Goin' places., 1977; SR-8703; Jacksons (Musical group) (Box 128)
      - 1001 - Africanism, 1977; SR-8704; Kongas (Musical group) (Box 128)
      - 1001 - Africanism, 1977; SR-8705; Kongas (Musical group) (Box 128)
        Crest International
        Australia
      - 1002 - Dance fantasy: inspired by Close encounters of the third kind, 1978; SR-8706; Montana, Vincent, Jr., 1928-2013. (Box 128)
      - Dance fantasy: inspired by Close encounters of the 3rd kind., 1978; SR-8707 (Box 128)
        Not numbered, housed with SR-8706.
        Atlantic/ATCO
      - 1003 - Spaced out disco., 1978; SR-8708 (Box 128)
        Springboard
      - 1004 - Radio active, 1978; SR-8709 (Box 128)
      - 1005 - Jam, 1978; SR-9246; Brown, James, 1933-2006. (Box 128)
      - 1008 - Percussion explosion, 1978; SR-8710; Herman Kelly & Life (Musical group) (Box 128)
        Edmar
      - 1008 - Percussion explosion, 1978; SR-8711; Herman Kelly & Life (Musical group) (Box 128)
        Electric Cat
      - 1009 - A whole new thing, Preston, Billy (Box 128)
      - 1010 - Rare Gems Odyssey., 1977; SR-8712-8713; Rare Gems Odyssey (Musical group) (Box 128)
        Promotional Copy, Not for Sale._x000D_ Matrix / Runout (A-side label): NBLP 7072 AS; Matrix / Runout (B-side label): NBLP 7072 BS.
      - 1010 - Rare Gems Odyssey., Rare Gems Odyssey (Musical group) (Box 128)
      - 1010 - Rare Gems Odyssey., Rare Gems Odyssey (Musical group) (Box 128)
      - 1011 - Secrets., 1977; SR-8714; Con-Funk-Shun (Musical group) (Box 128)
      - 1012 - Good, bad and funky, 1978; SR-8715; Shotgun (Musical group) (Box 128)
      - 1013 - Randy Pie., 1974; SR-8716; Randy Pie (Musical group) (Box 128)
      - 1014 - Platinum Hook., 1978; SR-8718 (Box 128)
      - 1014 - Platinum Hook., 1978; SR-8717 (Box 128)
      - 1015 - Reggae sampler., 1978; SR-9247-9248 (Box 128)
        United Artists Music and Records Group
      - 1016 - Cayenne, 1977; SR-8719 (Box 128)
      - 1017 - Number one man., 1978; SR-8720 (Box 128)
        Matrix / Runout (Side A run-out area): MN 7039 SNB-BK; Matrix / Runout (Side B run-out area): MN 7040 #2 SNB-BK.
        Total
      - 1017 - Number one man., 1978; SR-8721 (Box 129)
      - 1018 - We came to play., 1978; SR-8722-8723 (Box 129)
      - 1019 - Let's all chant, 1978; SR-8724; Zager, Michael. (Box 129)
      - 1020 - Cathedrals, 1976; SR-8725; LaRue, D. C. (Box 129)
      - 1021 - Man machine, 1978; SR-8626-8627; Kraftwerk (Musical group) (Box 129)
      - 1021 - Man machine, Kraftwerk (Musical group) (Box 129)
      - 1022 - Find a Friend, Kaygees (Box 129)
      - 1022 - Find a Friend, Kaygees (Box 129)
      - 1023 - Different moods of me, 1978; SR-6995; Jordan, Lonnie. (Box 129)
      - 1024 - Ghost town parade, 1978; SR-8728-8729; Dudek, Les. (Box 140)
      - 1025 - Let's get together, 1978; SR-8730; Detroit Emeralds (Musical group) (Box 129)
        Westbound Records; Distributed by Atlantic Recording Corp.
      - 1026 - Unemployment blues, 1976; SR-8731; Force of Nature (Musical group) (Box 129)
      - 1027 - Blood brother, blood sister, 1977; SR-9249; Black Blood (Musical group) (Box 129)
        "Demonstration, Not For Sale"
      - 1028 - Feel the phuff, 1978; SR-8732-8733; Manchild (Musical group) (Box 129)
      - 1030 - Brooklyn dreams., 1977; SR-8734; Brooklyn Dreams (Musical group) (Box 129)
      - 1031 - Ever ready (Box 129)
      - 1032 - It begins again, 1978; SR-8736; Springfield, Dusty. (Box 129)
      - 1032 - It begins again, 1978; SR-1032; Springfield, Dusty. (Box 129)
      - 1033 - American hot wax: the original soundtrack album from the Paramount motion picture., 1978; SR-8737-8738 (Box 129)
      - 1034 - Love, music and life, 1977; SR-8739; Rogers, D. J., 1948- (Box 129)
      - 1035 - More carnival, 1978; SR-8740; Lee, Byron. (Box 129)
      - 1036 - How much, how much I love you, 1978; SR-8741; Love & Kisses (Musical group) (Box 129)
        Casablanca Record and Filmworks
      - 1038 - Chicago Transit Authority., 1969; SR-8742-8743; Chicago (Musical group) (Box 129)
        Prologue, August 29, 1968: actual recording from the Democratic convention (Chicago, August 29, 1968). Black militants exhorting demonstrators: "God give us the blood to keep going"
      - 1039 - Rough diamond, 1978; SR-8744; Kane, Madleen. (Box 129)
      - 1040 - Central heating, 1978; SR-7757; Heatwave (Musical group), (Box 129)
      - 1041 - A-nal-y-sis, 1973; SR-9250-9251; Nite-Liters (Musical group) (Box 129)
      - 1042 - Kool & the Gang live at P.J.'s., 1971; SR-8745; Kool & the Gang. (Box 129)
      - 1042 - Kool and the Gang live at P.J.'s., 1971; SR-9252; Kool & the Gang. (Box 129)
      - 1043 - Ten years of gold, 1976; SR-8746; Franklin, Aretha. (Box 129)
      - 1045 - Dancing in the street, 1978; SR-8747; Trax (Musical group) (Box 129)
      - 1046 - Band together, 1978; SR-8748-8749; Rare Earth (Musical group) (Box 129)
      - 1047 - Mark, Don & Mel, 1969-71, 1972; SR-8750-8751; Grand Funk Railroad (Musical group) (Box 129)
      - 1048 - Tropea, 1975; SR-8753; Tropea, John. (Box 129)
        Marlin: Distributed by T.K. Productions
      - 1049 - Get to the feeling., 1978; SR-8754-8755 (Box 129)
      - 1049 - Get to the feeling., Pleasure (Box 129)
        Empry jacket.
      - 1050 - Phase II, 1977; SR-8756; Bohannon, Hamilton. (Box 129)
      - 1051 - Ralf & Florian, 1975; SR-6802; Kraftwerk (Musical group) (Box 3)
        This copy used on the Renegades of Rhythm Tour. Matrix / Runout (Run-out side A, stamped, etched): VEL-2006 A-CS5 MASTERDISK G.K. Matrix / Runout (Run-out side B, stamped, etched): VEL-2006 B-CS6 MASTERDISK G.K._x000D_
        Vertigo: Manufactured and distributed by Phonogram
      - 1053 - At the discotheque, 1978; SR-8757; Lipstique (Musical group) (Box 129)
        Tom n' Jerry Records
      - 1054 - Anvil Band., 1977; SR-8758; Anvil Band. (Box 129)
      - 1055 - Wild Tchoupitoulas., 1976; SR-8759; Wild Tchoupitoulas (Musical group) (Box 129)
      - 1056 - Future games, 1977; SR-8760; Spirit (Musical group) (Box 129)
      - 1057 - Wizard, 1968; SR-8761; Brown, Mel, 1939-2009. (Box 130)
      - 1058 - Betty Wright live., 1978; SR-8762; Wright, Betty, 1953- (Box 130)
        Alston Records
      - 1059 - Sweet ride, 1978; SR-8763-8764; Southroad Connection (Musical group), (Box 130)
        Mahogany
      - 1060 - Dance across the floor, 1978; SR-8765; Horne, Jimmy Bo. (Box 130)
        Sunshine Sound
      - 1061 - Bitch is bad, 1977; SR-9253; LaSalle, Denise. (Box 130)
      - 1062 - Natural high, 1978; SR-8766; Commodores (Musical group) (Box 130)
      - 1063 - Mandre¿¿ two., 1978; SR-8767; Mandre¿¿. (Box 130)
      - 1064 - Original motion picture soundtrack of Thank God it's Friday., 1978; SR-8768-SR-8770 (Box 130)
      - 1065 - Eli's Second Coming., 1977; SR-8771 (Box 130)
        Silver Blue
      - 1066 - Don't let the system get you., 1978; SR-8772 (Box 130)
      - 1067 - Come get it!., 1978; SR-8773; James, Rick, 1948-2004. (Box 130)
      - 1068 - Truth is on its way, 1974; SR-8774; Giovanni, Nikki. (Box 130)
        New York Community Choir under the direction of Benny Diggs._x000D_
        Right-On Records
      - 1069 - African-rhythm-machine., 1975; SR-8775; Dibango, Manu, 1933- (Box 130)
        Compilation of 7" tracks recorded in 1975, 1974, 1972 & 1971.
        Fiesta
      - 1070 - Winners., 1978; SR-8776 (Box 130)
      - 1071 - Africadelic, 1975; SR-9254; Dibango, Manu, 1933- (Box 130)
        FFRR
      - 1072 - Got a feeling, 1978; SR-8777; Juvet, Patrick (Vocalist) (Box 130)
        Casablanca Record and Film Works
      - 1073 - Funky Nassau, 1971; SR-8778; Beginning of the End (Musical group) (Box 130)
        Matrix / Runout (Label Side A): ST-C-712335 PR; Matrix / Runout (Label Side B): ST-C-712336 PR.
        Alston
      - 1074 - Fame, 1978; SR-8779; Jones, Grace. (Box 130)
      - 1074 - Fame, 1978; SR-8780; Jones, Grace. (Box 130)
      - 1075 - Return to Casablanca. Vol. II., 1978; SR-8781 (Box 130)
        Promotional copy._x000D_ Matrix / Runout (Side A Runout, Etched): NBD-20131-AS AZ S-5845; Matrix / Runou
      - 1076 - Whiter shade of pale, 1978; SR-8782; Munich Machine (Musical group) (Box 130)
      - 1077 - Perceptions, 1978; SR-8783; Earland, Charles. (Box 130)
      - 1078 - Seven deadly sins, 1977; SR-8785; Rinder, Laurin. (Box 130)
      - 1079 - Voyager, 1978; SR-8784; Wansel, Dexter. (Box 130)
      - 1080 - (Latin disco) Salsa's greatest hits, 1977; SR-9255 (Box 130)
        "Not For Sale."
      - 1081 - Gerson Combo, 1977; SR-8786-8787; Combo, Gerson King. (Box 130)
      - 1082 - That Larry Williams., 1978; SR-8788-8789 (Box 130)
      - 1083 - Summertime groove, 1978; SR-8790; Bohannon, Hamilton, (Box 130)
        Philips
      - 1084 - Love in a sleeper., 1978; SR-8791 (Box 130)
      - 1086 - My radio sure sounds good to me, 1978; SR-9256; Graham, Larry, 1946- (Box 130)
      - 1087 - Love brought me back., 1978; SR-8792 (Box 130)
      - 1088 - King of rock and roll, 1971; SR-8793; Little Richard, 1932- (Box 130)
      - 1089 - Ain't that enough for you., 1978; SR-8794 (Box 130)
      - 1090 - Love-a-thon., 1978; SR-8795 (Box 130)
      - 1091 - I wanna make it on my own., 1978; SR-8796-8797 (Box 130)
      - 1092 - Chicken lickin', Funk, Inc. (Box 130)
      - 1094 - Atlantic Starr., 1978; SR-8798 (Box 130)
      - 1096 - Three miles high., 1978; SR-8799-8800 (Box 130)
      - 1097 - Need to know you better., 1978; SR-8801-8802; Finished Touch (Musical group) (Box 130)
      - 1100 - From the gut to the butt., 1978; SR-8803 (Box 131)
      - 1103 - New warrior, 1978; SR-8804; Lyle, Bobby. (Box 131)
      - 1104 - Do it all night, 1978; SR-9258; Mayfield, Curtis. (Box 131)
      - 1104 - Do it all night, 1978; SR-9257; Mayfield, Curtis. (Box 131)
      - 1105 - Butterfly, 1979-1979; SR-8805-8806; Blowfly, 1939-2016. (Box 131)
      - 1106 - Music from the motion picture Convoy., 1978; SR-8826 (Box 131)
      - 1107 - Erotic moods, 1978; SR-8827; Winley, Paul, (Box 131)
      - 1108 - Charanga 76 live at Roseland, 1978; SR-9259; Charanga 76 (Musical group) (Box 131)
        T.R. Records
      - 1110 - Life is a song worth singing, 1978; SR-8828; Pendergrass, Teddy. (Box 131)
      - 1110 - Life is a song worth singing, 1978; SR-9649; Pendergrass, Teddy. (Box 140)
      - 1111 - Grand Funk, 1969; SR-8752; Grand Funk Railroad (Musical group), (Box 129)
      - 1112 - Kid's stuff, 1976; SR-8829-8830; Babe Ruth (Musical group) (Box 131)
      - 1113 - One., 1974; SR-8831-8832; James, Bob, 1939- (Box 131)
      - 1114 - Open the doors to your heart, 1978; SR-8833-8834; Barreiro, Jorge (Composer) (Box 131)
      - 1115 - Youngblood: original motion picture soundtrack, 1978; SR-8835 (Box 131)
      - 1115 - Youngblood: original motion picture soundtrack, 1978; SR-8836 (Box 131)
      - 1116 - Ain't no backin' up now, 1975; SR-8837; Isis (Musical group) (Box 131)
      - 1119 - Sweet taste of sin, 1978; SR-8838-8839; Dennis Coffey Band. (Box 131)
      - 1120 - Big T.V. hits!, 1977; SR-8840 (Box 131)
      - 1121 - Back in Time., 1978; SR-8841; Back in Time (Musical group) (Box 131)
      - 1122 - You send me, 1978; SR-8842; Ayers, Roy. (Box 131)
      - 1124 - Whatcha see is whatcha get., 1970-1979; SR-8843 (Box 131)
      - 1125 - Brand New Funk '78, 1978; SR-8844-8845; Brand New Funk (Musical group) (Box 131)
        Vibration
      - 1126 - Barry White the man, 1978; SR-9260; White, Barry, 1944-2003. (Box 131)
      - 1128 - Quartz., 1978; SR-8846 (Box 131)
      - 1129 - Magic bimbo., 1975; SR-8847 (Box 131)
      - 1131 - Flying start, 1974; SR-8848-8849; Blackbyrds (Musical group) (Box 131)
      - 1131 - Flying start, Blackbyrds (Musical group) (Box 131)
      - 1133 - One nation under a groove, 1978; SR-9261; Funkadelic (Musical group) (Box 131)
      - 1138 - Let your soul fly, 1976; SR-8850; Mafalme. (Box 131)
        Also issued as Jimmie Raye's The soul thing.
        Asante
      - 1139 - Reinforcements, 1975; SR-8851; Oblivion Express (Musical group) (Box 131)
      - 1141 - Togetherness, 1978; SR-8852; L.T.D. (Musical group) (Box 131)
      - 1142 - Ollie Baba, 1978; SR-8853-8854 (Box 131)
      - 1143 - Goin' coconuts., 1978; SR-8855 (Box 131)
      - 1145 - Kenny Brawner & Raw Sugar., 1978; SR-9262 (Box 131)
        Pyramid/UA
      - 1145 - Kenny Brawner & Raw Sugar., 1978; SR-8856 (Box 131)
      - 1146 - Take it on up, 1978; SR-8857; Pockets (Musical group) (Box 131)
      - 1147 - Under the influence, 1978; SR-8858; LaSalle, Denise. (Box 131)
      - 1147 - Under the influence, 1978; SR-8859; LaSalle, Denise. (Box 131)
      - 1148 - Chanson., 1978; SR-8860; Chanson (Musical group). (Box 131)
      - 1149 - Rough, 1978; SR-8861; Turner, Tina. (Box 131)
      - 1150 - It's a new day so let a man come in, 1970; SR-8862; Brown, James, 1933-2006. (Box 132)
      - 1151 - Burnin', 1978; SR-8863; Douglas, Californiarol. (Box 132)
      - 1152 - Headlights, 1978; SR-8864; Whispers (Musical group), (Box 132)
        Solar Records
      - 1152 - Headlights, 1978; SR-8865; Whispers (Musical group), (Box 132)
      - 1154 - Sly, Slick & Wicked., 1976; SR-9263 (Box 132)
      - 1155 - Garden of love, 1978; SR-9264; Ray, Don (Vocalist), (Box 132)
      - 1156 - Patti LaBelle., 1977; SR-9265 (Box 132)
      - 1157 - I wrote a simple song, 1971; SR-9266; Preston, Billy. (Box 132)
      - 1158 - Breakin' it, 1977; SR-9267; Law (Musical group) (Box 132)
      - 1159 - For you, 1978; SR-9268; Prince. (Box 132)
      - 1161 - K.C. and the Sunshine Band., 1978; SR-9269; KC & the Sunshine Band. (Box 132)
      - 1161 - K.C. and the Sunshine Band., 1978; SR-9270; KC & the Sunshine Band. (Box 132)
      - 1162 - Kiss this world goodbye, 1978; SR-9271; Mtume. (Box 132)
        Zembu
      - 1163 - Adventures of Captain Sky, 1978; SR-9272; Captain Sky. (Box 132)
        "Promo copy; Not for Sale."
      - 1163 - Adventures of Captain Sky, 1978; SR-9273; Captain Sky. (Box 132)
      - Adventures of Captain Sky, 1978; SR-9274-9275; Captain Sky. (Box 132)
        Not numbered, housed with SR-9273
      - 1163 - Adventures of Captain Sky, 1978; SR-9276-9277; Captain Sky. (Box 132)
      - 1164 - Money talks., 1978; SR-9278; Bar-Kays (Musical group) (Box 132)
        Stax Records; Distributed by Fantasy Records
      - 1165 - Keep on jumpin', 1978; SR-9279 (Box 132)
      - 1168 - Everybody's dancin', 1978; SR-9280 (Box 132)
      - 1169 - Down in the village, 1971; SR-9281; Knight, Curtis. (Box 132)
      - 1170 - Love somebody, 1978; SR-9283; Bisso, Jo. (Box 132)
      - 1170 - Love somebody, 1978; SR-9282; Bisso, Jo. (Box 132)
      - 1171 - Midnight express: music from the original motion picture soundtrack, 1978; SR-9284; Moroder, Giorgio. (Box 132)
      - 1172 - Writers., 1978; SR-9286; Writers (Musical group) (Box 132)
      - 1172 - Writers., 1978; SR-9285; Writers (Musical group) (Box 132)
      - 1173 - Street corner symphony, 1978; SR-9287; Lucas, Californiarrie. (Box 132)
      - 1174 - In tune, 1978; SR-9288; Hutch, Willie. (Box 132)
        Warner Brothers Records/Whitfield
      - 1175 - Live and more, 1978; SR-9289-9290; Summer, Donna. (Box 132)
        Casablanca Record and Filmworks: NBLP 7119-2 (on container: NBLP 7119)._x000D_
      - 1178 - Fire., 1978; SR-9291; Fire (Musical group) (Box 132)
      - 1179 - Our Ms. Brooks, 1978; SR-9292; Brooks, Pattie. (Box 132)
      - 1180 - Future star, 1978; SR-9293; Sins of Satan (Musical group) (Box 132)
      - 1182 - Livetime, 1978; SR-9294-9295; Hall and Oates. (Box 132)
      - 1183 - Give thankx, 1978; SR-9296; Cliff, Jimmy. (Box 132)
      - 1184 - Bell & James., 1978; SR-9297; Bell & James (Musical group), (Box 132)
        White label; promotional copy._x000D_
      - 1185 - Sweet, sweet city rhythm, 1978; SR-9298; Fantasia (Disco group) (Box 132)
        Amazon
      - 1187 - Warmer communications, 1978; SR-9299; Average White Band. (Box 132)
      - 1188 - SofTouch., 1978; SR-9300; SofTouch (Musical group) (Box 132)
      - 1189 - Hearts of stone, 1978; SR-9301; Stoneground (Musical group) (Box 132)
      - 1190 - Spacin out, 1978; SR-9302; Fat Larry's Band. (Box 132)
      - 1191 - Greatest hits, 1977; SR-9303; Bay City Rollers, (Box 133)
      - 1192 - Single man., 1978; SR-9304; John, Elton. (Box 133)
      - 1195 - Clean, 1978; SR-9305; Starr, Edwin. (Box 133)
      - 1196 - Disco gardens., 1978; SR-9306; Shalamar (Musical group) (Box 133)
      - 1197 - Spreading love, 1978; SR-9307-9308; Hudson, Al. (Box 133)
      - 1198 - Golden touch, 1978; SR-9309-9310; Cerrone. (Box 133)
      - 1199 - Walking on sunshine, 1978; SR-9311; Grant, Eddy, (Box 133)
        Human
      - 1199 - Walking on sunshine, 1978; SR-9332; Grant, Eddy, (Box 133)
        ICE
      - 1200 - Quazar., 1978; SR-9312; Quazar (Musical group) (Box 133)
      - 1201 - Concept, 1978; SR-9313-9314; Slave (Musical group) (Box 133)
      - 1202 - I'm in you; Black coco, 1978; SR-9316; Samba Soul (Musical group) (Box 133)
        Promotional copy issued in translucent blue vinyl._x000D_ From the RCA album, Do it, APL1-2991.
      - 1202 - Do it, 1978; SR-9315; Samba Soul (Musical group) (Box 133)
      - I'm in you; Black coco, 1978; SR-9317; Samba Soul (Musical group) (Box 133)
        Not numbered, housed with SR-9316. Issued in translucent blue vinyl._x000D_ From the RCA album, Do it, APL1-2991.
      - 1203 - Rhythm of life, 1978; SR-9318; Love Child's Afro-Cuban Blues Band. (Box 133)
      - 1204 - Funk or walk, 1978; SR-9319; Brides of Funkenstein (Musical group) (Box 133)
      - 1205 - Goin' for myself, 1972; SR-9320; Coffey, Dennis. (Box 133)
      - 1206 - Guess Who live at the Paramount., 1972; SR-9321; Guess Who (Musical group) (Box 133)
      - 1207 - Kryptonite, 1975; SR-9322; Merryweather, Neil. (Box 133)
      - 1209 - Wilson Pickett in Philadelphia., 1970; SR-9323-9324; Pickett, Wilson. (Box 133)
      - 1210 - Throw down, 1978; SR-9325; Voltage Brothers. (Box 133)
        Liberty/United Artists Records
      - 1211 - Reunion: live at Madison Square Garden: 1972, 1973; SR-9327; Dion, 1939- (Box 133)
      - 1212 - Hot butterfly, 1978; SR-9334; Diamond, Gregg. (Box 133)
      - 1213 - Gaz, 1978; SR-6761; Gaz (Musical group) (Box 1)
        This copy used on the Renegades of Rhythm Tour. Housed with SR-6760.
      - 1213 - Gaz, Gaz (Musical group) (Box 133)
      - 1214 - You ain't no friend of mine!., 1978; SR-9335-9336 (Box 133)
      - 1215 - Sufficiently breathless, 1977; SR-9337; Dorman, Lee, 1942-2012. (Box 133)
        Reissue of: CP-0115 (1973)._x000D_ Promotional copy._x000D_
      - 1217 - Destiny, 1978; SR-9338; Jacksons (Musical group) (Box 133)
      - 1218 - Organized Con-Funk-Shun., 1978; SR-9339 (Box 133)
      - 1219 - Kinsman Dazz., 1978; SR-9340; Kinsman Dazz (Musical group) (Box 133)
      - 1222 - Any way you want it., 1978; SR-9341 (Box 133)
        Ariola
      - 1223 - My claim to fame, 1978; SR-9342; Wells, James, 1956- (Box 133)
      - 1224 - We're the Banana Splits., 1968; SR-9343; Banana Splits (Musical group) (Box 133)
      - 1225 - Village People, 1977; SR-9344; Village People, (Box 133)
      - 1226 - Sho is funky down here, 1971; SR-9345; Brown, James, 1933-2006. (Box 133)
        Starday-King Records
      - 1227 - On the road again, 1978; SR-9346; Rockets (Musical group: France) (Box 133)
        Promotional Copy, Not For Sale.
        Tom 'n Jerry
      - 1228 - City lights, 1978; SR-9347 (Box 133)
      - 1230 - All about Esther Phillips., 1978; SR-9348; Phillips, Esther, 1935-1984. (Box 133)
      - 1231 - Band of gypsys, 1970; SR-9349; Hendrix, Jimi. (Box 133)
      - 1232 - Night to remember., 1977; SR-9350 (Box 133)
      - 1233 - Rhythm of life., 1977; SR-9351 (Box 133)
        Chiaroscuro
      - 1234 - Three., 1976; SR-9352 (Box 133)
      - 1235 - Giant, 1978; SR-9353; Watson, Johnny "Guitar", 1935-1996. (Box 133)
        DJM Records
        Buffalo, New York
      - 1236 - Proud one., 1975; SR-9354 (Box 134)
        MGM/Kolob Records
      - 1238 - Kids are people too, 1971; SR-9355; McAllister, Bob. (Box 134)
        Roulette Records
      - 1241 - In the night-time., 1978; SR-9356-9357 (Box 134)
      - 1242 - Urban renewal, 1974; SR-9358; Tower of Power (Musical group) (Box 134)
      - 1243 - First cuckoo, 1975; SR-1243; Deodato, Eumir. (Box 134)
      - 1245 - White Heat., 1975; SR-9360; White Heat (Musical group) (Box 134)
      - 1246 - Upp., 1975; SR-9361-9362; Upp (Musical group) (Box 134)
      - 1249 - No Slack., 1978; SR-9363-9364 (Box 134)
      - 1252 - Don't let up, 1976; SR-9365; Olympic Runners (Musical group) (Box 134)
      - 1253 - Out in front, 1975; SR-9366; Olympic Runners (Musical group) (Box 134)
      - 1254 - Put the music where your mouth is, 1974; SR-9367-9368; Olympic Runners (Musical group) (Box 134)
      - 1255 - Grand slam, 1978; SR-9369; Rare Earth (Musical group) (Box 134)
        Matrix / Runout (Runout Side 1): P7-10027R1A-18B; Matrix / Runout (Runout Side 2): P7-10027R1B-18B.
        Prodical
      - 1256 - I love my music., 1978; SR-9370 (Box 134)
      - 1257 - Take a look at those cakes, 1978; SR-9371; Brown, James, 1933-2006. (Box 134)
      - 1258 - Motor-booty affair., 1978; SR-9372 (Box 134)
      - 1259 - Love tracks., 1978; SR-9373 (Box 134)
      - 1260 - Brass Construction IV, 1978; SR-9374; Brass Construction (Musical group) (Box 134)
      - 1261 - Step in to our life, 1978; SR-9375; Ayers, Roy. (Box 134)
      - 1264 - Dizzy, 1969; SR-9376; Roe, Tommy. (Box 134)
      - 1265 - Bob McAllister of wonderama, 1968; SR-9377; McAllister, Bob. (Box 134)
      - 1266 - Dredlocks satisfaction, 1979; SR-9378; Trinity (Musician) (Box 134)
        Charmers
      - 1267 - Tender is the night, 1978; SR-9379-9380; THP Orchestra (Box 134)
      - 1268 - Babe Ruth., 1975; SR-9381; Babe Ruth (Musical group) (Box 134)
        Harvest
      - 1269 - I love music, 1978; SR-9382; Montana (Musical group) (Box 134)
      - 1271 - Symphony of love, 1978; SR-9383; Mason, Barry, 1935- (Box 134)
      - 1272 - Bloody tourists, 1978; SR-9384; 10cc (Musical group) (Box 134)
      - 1274 - Gotcha, 1978; SR-9385; Smith, Lonnie, 1942- (Box 134)
        Lord Shorty Enterprises: Distributed by Charlie's Records
      - 1275 - Rudy Copeland., 1978; SR-9386; Copeland, Rudy. (Box 134)
      - 1276 - Disco dancin', 1978; SR-9387-9388-9389; Studio 78 (Musical group) (Box 134)